Kettle and Idol
3rd obsession
obsession
Oh, so you're an obsessive girl?
I'm often told that I'm a little obsessive, a little obsessive in a weird way.
Yes, I do.
For example, I like to keep things clean.
A bit neat?
Yes, not quite neat, but a bit neat.
It's not so much that I like to keep my viewers clean.
Yes, I don't mind a messy room.
I have a thing about pajamas and loungewear.
Heh.
I change my clothes seven times a day.
Really? Really?
Yes.
That's private, right?
Private.
So, first thing in the morning, you get up.
I get dressed.
But first, you change out of your pajamas, which are not your regular clothes.
It's a dinner jersey.
Is that right?
Yes, sir.
Then you change into the jerseys you wear to get ready after you finish eating.
And then you change into the jersey you wear to clean yourself up.
No, not for eating.
No, sir.
What?
You know, to get close to the water.
You wash your face.
A little toothpaste might splash on it.
Or lotion might fall off.
I really want to keep the table clean for eating.
Clean for eating
That's why I changed my clothes.
This is the second time.
And the last one from jerseys.
When I'm all dressed up, I change into my clothes.
And then I go out.
And I come back.
And then I change from plain clothes to a regular jersey.
Yes, four times
Yes, four times.
And after that
I change into a jersey for eating dinner.
I see.
I never go outside in the jersey for eating.
Then, I change.
Then, you take a bath, right?
I'm going to take a bath.
And after taking a bath...
You change into pajamas for the whole day.
What?
The whole set of pajamas.
You change into a pair of pajamas.
Get yourself cleaned up.
That's six.
Yes, and one more change into pajamas before bed.
Round 2
Change into two pairs of pajamas, and that's it.
Heh.
So, do you eat breakfast and dinner together?
Morning and evening are the same.
The same.
Yes, I almost never wash the pajamas.
What?
The pajamas.
I don't wash the rest.
I don't wash them, I just change them.
I think I wash them because I wear them for a long time.
So they get dirty for a long time.
That's why we split them up.
There you go.
I thought it would work.
But you only wear it for a short time.
That's right.
The laundry cycle is about a week.
No, a month or two.
Oh, no, a week.Oh, a week for a week
Oh, a month
One month, two months
Long
One month, two months.
Well, that's quite a special habit you have.
But he never changes out of that HEATTECH.
Heatech doesn't change.
That HEATTECH every day.
More and more and more and more.
It's like, if I go here, he won't look back.
What kind of...
But why do you never change the basis of anything?
I don't need to wash it.
It's the way of thinking.
Yes.
You're very particular.
You want to wash it.
No, you don't.
Oh, you don't.
No, I don't.
You don't, do you?
Yes, I do.
It's an obsession, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's a bit of an obsession.
What are pajamas 1 and 2?
You're taking a bath, right?
You sweat a little after taking a bath, don't you?
I don't like sleeping in sweaty pajamas.
I see.
When I'm close to you, I don't want anything bouncing on me.
You're particular about that?
No, I don't want even a little bit of lotion on them.
That's right.
I see.
I'm a bit of a stickler.
Since you were a kid?
It never goes away, it's always been that way.
Oh, so that's what it is.
I'm on my own.
Like azuki bean washers washing azuki beans?
All the time.
That's what it's like.
It doesn't matter what I say...
Maybe it's a demon
Monster
Are you a demon?
No, no, no
Thank you very much
Then Haruma's three obsessions
loudness, charm, and persistence.
Thank you very much
Yes, I understand.
Uh...
Huh?
This program is...
Mr. Shou
Mr. Chitty
Mr. Poyo
Mr. Umauma
Mr. Koguchi
Thank you very much!